(Raj:)In case you didn't follow that,
I'm the coffee.
Leonard, maybe you'd like to go
with them to meet girls.
(Leonard:)Why would I be interested?
I have Penny.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, for now.
(Sheldon:)But that woman has a death wish,
Leonard.
Yeah, she talks to strangers,
she pets unfamiliar dogs...
(Sheldon:)...and it is ridiculously easy
to break into her apartment.
(Sheldon:)If I were you, I'd get a backup.
(Leonard:)You can't just replace someone you care
about with some other random person.
Uh, please don't ruin this for me.
(Sheldon:)Do you remember how upset I was...
(Sheldon:)...when they replaced
Edward Norton as the Hulk?
(Leonard:)Yes, you walked around for a week...
(Leonard:)...saying,
"Sheldon unhappy with casting choice."
(Sheldon:)But then Mark Ruffalo was the Hulk
in The Avengers and he was even better.
- What's your point?
- Call me a romantic.
(Sheldon:)I like to think that your Mark Ruffalo
is still out there somewhere.